pgimprovinglife.com 2012-06-25

# P&G Privacy Notice

P&G Privacy Notice

This Privacy Notice applies to information, including personal information, collected about you by **P &G (The Procter & Gamble Company and its affiliated companies and subsidiaries)**

  * We collect information about you from a variety of sources, including:
  * Information we collect from you directly.
  * Information we collect about you when you visit our site, use our services, or view our online advertisements.
  * Information we collect about you from other sources, such as commercially available sources.

  * All the information we collect about you may be combined to help us tailor our communications to you and to develop world-class products and services.

  * We use the information we collect to provide the products and services you request, to tell you about other products and services offered by P&G, and to manage our sites and services.
  * In general, we do not share your personal information with third-party marketers, unless we have asked for and obtained your explicit consent.
  * We may share your information:
  * With our third-party service suppliers, including those who work on behalf of P&G and our business partners to send you joint communications that we hope you find of interest.
  * If a P&G brand is sold to another company.
  * To protect and defend the right and property of P&G (including enforcing our Terms and Conditions).
  * When required by law, and / or public authorities.

  * We give you choices about how we communicate with you.
  * You can stop receiving promotional email or postal communications from a particular P&G brand or program through this Privacy Notice. Please [click here](http://www.pg.com/privacy/contact_us/contact_us/privacy-central-contact-interactive.html) to select your country and learn how to complete your request.
  * [Click here](http://www.pg.com/privacy/contact_us/contact_us/privacy-central-contact-interactive.html) to select your country and learn how to access and update the contact information you provided P&G.

  * P&G is committed to working with consumers to obtain a fair resolution of any complaint or concern about privacy.
  * P&G complies with country data protection laws.
  * We cooperate with country data protection authorities if they believe a privacy problem has occurred.
  * We participate in the US Council of [**Better Business Bureau's (BBB)**](https://www.bbb.org/online/consumer/cks.aspx?ID=292000103) Accredited Business Program and BBB EU Safe Harbor Dispute Resolution.

  * To contact us with a question [**click here**](http://www.pg.com/privacy/contact_us/contact_us/privacy-central-contact-interactive.html)(for country specific addresses)  
Or write to us at:  
P&G Global Privacy Team  
PO Box 599  
Cincinnati, OH 45202  
USA
  * To read our full Consumer Privacy Statement **click here.**
  * To read our Global Privacy Policy [**click here.**](http://www.pg.com/en_US/sustainability/privacy/global_privacy_policy.shtml)
  * **Click here** to view Answers to Frequently Asked Questions
